[
	{
		"question": "What is the loudest insect in the world?",
		"options": [
			"Bee",
			"Cicada",
			"Wasp",
			"Mantis"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "Which bird lays the smallest egg?",
		"options": [
			"Hummingbird",
			"Finches",
			"Goldcrest ",
			"Raven"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "Which ant has the most painful sting?",
		"options": [
			"Black Carpenter Ant",
			"Meat Ant",
			"Electric Ant",
			"Bullet Ant"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "What is the larvae stage of a frog called?",
		"options": [
			"Toad",
			"Metamorphosis",
			"Froglet",
			"Tadpole"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "What feature is visibly different between alligators and crocodiles?",
		"options": [
			"Tail",
			"Snout",
			"Eyes",
			"Tongue"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "How many compartments are in a cow's stomach?",
		"options": [
			"One",
			"Two",
			"Three",
			"Four"
		],
		"answer": 3
	},
	{
		"question": "What color is a polar bear's skin?",
		"options": [
			"White",
			"Black",
			"Yellow",
			"Brown"
		],
		"answer": 1
	},
	{
		"question": "What bird buries it's head in the ground?",
		"options": [
			"Turkey",
			"Hen",
			"Ostrich",
			"Penguin"
		],
		"answer": 2
	},
	{
		"question": "What object does a male penguin often gift to a female penguin to win her over?",
		"options": [
			"A Pebble",
			"Block of Ice",
			"Fish",
			"None of the above"
		],
		"answer": 0
	},
	{
		"question": "What are a group of crows called?",
		"options": [
			"Black",
			"Pack",
			"Murder",
			"School"
		],
		"answer": 2
	}
]